http://www.oslinmd.com/privacy-policy

Menu
Call (615) 234-3223
HOMEPROCEDURESBreast ProceduresFacial ProceduresBody Contouring ProceduresOther ProceduresPHOTOSABOUT DR. OSLINFORMSMedical History FormOslin Office Face SheetCONTACT
Oslin Plastic Surgery Privacy Policy
Last updated: January 1, 2019Oslin Plastic Surgery, PLLC operates www.oslinmd.com and related social media pages (Sites). This document informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Sites.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information Collection And UseWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").Log DataLike many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data").This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics and Facebook Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information. These tools may include cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels and local shared objects.We use log files, tags and tracking technologies to collect and analyze technical information including:• IP addresses• Device type• Operating System• MAC, IDFA, IMEI• Browser type• Browser language• Referring and exit pages with URLs• Quantity of clicks on a page or feature• Domain names• Landing pages• Pages viewed and order of those pages• Time spent on particular pages• Date and time of activity on our pages. CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include but is not limited to your email address. We collect this information for the purpose of providing the service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests and inquiries and improving our services.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
